<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<eml:eml xmlns:eml="eml://ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.1.1" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
         xsi:schemaLocation="eml://ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.1.1 http://rs.gbif.org/schema/eml-gbif-profile/1.1/eml.xsd"
        packageId="10.15468/dl.qaagaq"  system="http://gbif.org" scope="system"
  xml:lang="en">

<dataset>
        <alternateIdentifier>0140638-220831081235567</alternateIdentifier>
    <title>GBIF Occurrence Download 10.15468/dl.qaagaq</title>
    <creator>
    <individualName>
          <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
    </individualName>
<electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>    </creator>
    <metadataProvider>
    <individualName>
          <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
    </individualName>
<electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>    </metadataProvider>
      <pubDate>
      2022-11-04
      </pubDate>
    <language>ENGLISH</language>
    <abstract>
        <para>A dataset containing all occurrences available in GBIF matching the query:
{
  &quot;and&quot; : [
    &quot;BasisOfRecord is Human Observation&quot;,
    &quot;DatasetKey is Swiss National Databank of Vascular Plants&quot;,
    &quot;TaxonKey is one of (Eriophorum vaginatum L., Eriophorum vaginatum Curtis, Eriophorum brachyantherum × vaginatum, Eriophorum vaginatum subsp. vaginatum, Eriophorum brachyantherum x vaginatum, Eriophorum vaginatum var. brachyantherum (Trautv. &amp; C.A.Mey.) Krylov, Eriophorum vaginatum f. erubescens (Fernald) B.Boivin, Eriophorum vaginatum var. vaginatum, Eriophorum vaginatum var. fauriei (E.G.Camus) Kitag., Eriophorum vaginatum subsp. fauriei (E.G.Camus) Á.Löve &amp; D.Löve, Murbeckiella pinnatifida (Lam.) Rothm., Murbeckiella pinnatifida var. peyrusiana (Des Moul.) O.Bolòs &amp; Vigo, Murbeckiella pinnatifida subsp. herminii (Rivas Mart.) Greuter &amp; Burdet, Murbeckiella pinnatifida subsp. boryi (Boiss.) Maire, Murbeckiella pinnatifida subsp. pinnatifida, Dianthus sylvestris Boiss., Dianthus sylvestris Wulfen, Dianthus sylvestris subsp. kozjakensis Micevski, Dianthus sylvestris subsp. bertisceus Rech.fil., Dianthus sylvestris subsp. alboroseus F.K.Mey., Dianthus sylvestris subsp. longibracteatus (Maire) Greuter &amp; Burdet, Dianthus sylvestris subsp. boissieri (Willk.) Dobignard, Dianthus sylvestris subsp. aristidis (Batt.) Greuter &amp; Burdet, Dianthus sylvestris subsp. godronianus (Jord.) Gamisans, Dianthus sylvestris f. albiflorus Micevski)&quot;
  ]
}
The dataset includes records from the following constituent datasets. The full metadata for each constituent is also included in this archive:
13192 records from Swiss National Databank of Vascular Plants</para>
    </abstract>
      <contact>
    <individualName>
          <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
    </individualName>
<electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>      </contact>

</dataset>

<additionalMetadata>
    <metadata>
      <gbif>
        <dateStamp>2022-11-04T20:58:47Z</dateStamp>
      <citation identifier="10.15468/dl.qaagaq">GBIF Occurrence Download 10.15468/dl.qaagaq</citation>
              <physical>
                  <objectName>Darwin Core Archive</objectName>
                  <characterEncoding>UTF-8</characterEncoding>
                  <dataFormat>
                      <externallyDefinedFormat>
                          <formatName>Darwin Core Archive</formatName>
                      </externallyDefinedFormat>
                  </dataFormat>
                  <distribution>
                      <online>
                          <url function="download">https://api.gbif.org/v1/occurrence/download/request/0140638-220831081235567.zip</url>
                      </online>
                  </distribution>
              </physical>
      </gbif>
    </metadata>
</additionalMetadata>

</eml:eml>
